{
  "Classes" : {
    "zkvys5" : {
      "answer" : {
        "31" : [ {
          "answer" : "C",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "B",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        } ],
        "100" : [ {
          "answer" : "C",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "Mahir ki vxd?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "\nTarin kar?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        } ],
        "1001" : {
          "2" : {
            "answer" : "A",
            "question" : "Mahir ki vxd?",
            "verdict" : "Correct"
          }
        },
        "10001" : [ {
          "answer" : "B",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "D",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "Mahir ki vxd?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "\nTarin kar?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        } ],
        "2016331012" : [ {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "B",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "C",
          "question" : "Mahir ki vxd?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "D",
          "question" : "\nTarin kar?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        } ],
        "2016331031" : [ {
          "answer" : "D",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "D",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        } ],
        "2016331037" : [ {
          "answer" : "C",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        } ],
        "2016331072" : [ {
          "answer" : "C",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "B",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        } ],
        "20162829292992" : [ {
          "answer" : "B",
          "question" : "2+2 =?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "2+3 =? ",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "A",
          "question" : "Mahir ki vxd?",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        }, {
          "answer" : "D",
          "question" : "\nTarin kar?",
          "verdict" : "Wrong"
        }, {
          "answer" : "B",
          "question" : "bokachoda dipto\n",
          "verdict" : "Correct"
        } ]
      },
      "participants" : {
        "1565093828041" : {
          "2016331072" : "1"
        },
        "1565093878542" : {
          "2016331037" : "1"
        },
        "1565100144665" : {
          "31" : "1"
        },
        "1565115501118" : {
          "100" : "1"
        },
        "1565170102563" : {
          "10001" : "1"
        },
        "1565618100316" : {
          "2016331012" : "1"
        },
        "1566977398627" : {
          "20162829292992" : "1"
        }
      },
      "questions" : {
        "1565091232251" : {
          "ca" : "C",
          "opa" : "1",
          "opb" : "22",
          "opc" : "4",
          "opd" : "5",
          "question" : "2+2 =?"
        },
        "1565093543059" : {
          "ca" : "A",
          "opa" : "5",
          "opb" : "0",
          "opc" : "10",
          "opd" : "6",
          "question" : "2+3 =? "
        },
        "1565113037041" : {
          "ca" : "A",
          "opa" : "হ্যা",
          "opb" : "না",
          "opc" : "na",
          "opd" : "na",
          "question" : "Mahir ki vxd?"
        },
        "1565114343678" : {
          "ca" : "A",
          "opa" : "Asif er ",
          "opb" : "Onno karo",
          "opc" : "Onno karo",
          "opd" : "Onno karo",
          "question" : "\nTarin kar?"
        },
        "1566977312409" : {
          "ca" : "B",
          "opa" : "snsn",
          "opb" : "ndn",
          "opc" : "dnbd",
          "opd" : "sbsbs",
          "question" : "bokachoda dipto\n"
        }
      },
      "result" : {
        "1565093828348" : {
          "marks" : "1",
          "reg" : "2016331072"
        },
        "1565093878828" : {
          "marks" : "2",
          "reg" : "2016331037"
        },
        "1565100145014" : {
          "marks" : "1",
          "reg" : "31"
        },
        "1565115501416" : {
          "marks" : "4",
          "reg" : "100"
        },
        "1565170102845" : {
          "marks" : "2",
          "reg" : "10001"
        },
        "1565618100615" : {
          "marks" : "0",
          "reg" : "2016331012"
        },
        "1566977398976" : {
          "marks" : "3",
          "reg" : "20162829292992"
        }
      }
    }
  },
  "users" : {
    "UBKENAQm1iOTIeHzwR9XQCIpOwp1" : {
      "vf3g7O" : {
        "className" : "C",
        "code" : "vf3g7O"
      },
      "xAHY8t" : {
        "className" : "os",
        "code" : "xAHY8t"
      },
      "zkvys5" : {
        "className" : "cse 334",
        "code" : "zkvys5"
      }
    }
  }
}
